LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
There is a restless ghost wandering in this city.
The ghost is named Capitalism.
Fully
Automated
Capitalism
Nonflammable recycling preparation is done.
How about you?
Oh, whenever you're ready.
I don't know why the Major is being so cautious.
Our communications won't be tapped;
we don't need to use secret codes.
If we're not careful,
we might be caught off guard.
Even if the information was
wrong, gangsters are gangsters;
I don't see any way they could defeat us.
Tachikoma, what's the situation?
We finished closing the road!
Major! There's an old man in the garbage
here, what should we do?
Leave him alone, that's the precinct’s job.
What about there?
I've pulled out half of
the weird car's plug wires.
Should I pull out this car's plug wires too?
Let's go.
It is indeed Japanese-made, very sensitive.
Sanitation Department...
we're here to collect bulky trash.
If it's a mistake,
I'd like you to sign here please...
Don't move, and be quiet.
The authorities have already learned
of your plan to attack a financial institution.
Resistance is futile.
Didn't we tell you...
not to resist?
Okay, take them away.
The information was right,
nothing worse than a shotgun.
We should wrap this case
up quickly and cautiously.
Major!
Are you okay?
You're alive for the time being.
Now is not the time to laugh.
Togusa, turn the car around.
Be careful.
Yes, there was one Senkousha android
mixed in with them.
And?
The mastermind is a gangster
from the Henan Province,
he wanted to get revenge for the money he
lost when Interstar sold its own stock.
You look terrible.
Is your goal to draw my gaze?
That can't be...
there's no need.
Was the information from the Henan Province
Department of Public Safety useful?
There are two things that I'm concerned about.
One is the Android that was
there but not in the report.
But that's not the big problem.
Really?
The other is...
their goal should have been to
attack a financial institution,
so why did they have data
on an individual investor?
Who is it?
Yokose Kanemoto.
He was originally a mathematician,
but now he's one of the world's richest men.
He's a big investor who is involved
in every big speculative deal.
That is to say, he's a corporate racketeer.
I've heard his name before.
Dealing with numbers wasn't
enough of a challenge for him,
so he started playing the stock market.
He seems to have a talent for it.
But he treats electronic money and
stocks as if they are just a game.
More than that, he seems to have a perverse obsession with collecting
gold, and he has amassed an enormous amount.
But, he doesn't like publicity
and he rarely takes centre stage.
Therefore, he's called "Crow Tengu".
So, he must have many enemies.
Strange man, isn't he?
You sure seem to know a lot,
are you buying stock now?
No, I just happened to see a TV show
called "Luxurious Mansions of the World".
You sure are a family man...
Chief, it's a transmission from Mr. Wan of the
Huanan Province Public Safety Bureau.
Hmm, connect to it with double security measures.
Roger.
Aramaki-San, it's been a while,
since the Asia Public Safety Conference, right?
We apologise for the trouble in this case.
This brings shame to our
country, I must apologise.
No, fortunately we handled it at the last minute.
What's happening today?
Actually, after investigating the bank accounts of the
people who smuggled weapons to the gangsters,
we saw an unexplained transaction.
From past experience, I think this is
evidence that they hired a mafia gunman,
so I wanted to let you know right away.
Thank you for your trouble.
We will carefully plan how to handle it.
Thank you so much.
Just to be sure, watch Yokose Kanemoto.
Batou will go to the heliport
with Ishikawa and equip with D3.
Load up one Tachikoma.
Togusa will re-interrogate the gangsters.
Use whatever methods necessary.
From A-SIA to ¥€$?
I believe the exchange rate for Yen
would be more favorable...
I don't mind.
Just a moment please.
Ishikawa-San, let me play with it too.
Major...
I can't find any contact information for Yokose.
That's unlike you.
File a legal brief and see which lawyers respond.
You should be able to find
information through them.
Even major banks have corporate
officers who are responsible.
Nope, that trick didn't catch anything.
Actually, he's an enigma.
Not only is he not cyberized,
even his chief manager doesn't have his contact information,
neither on his mobile devices nor his computer.
What about the producer of
that luxurious mansions show?
He should know the contact information, right?
I tried that too,
but it seems like Yokose was the one
who initiated all contact during the interviews.
So the big mansion is all you know about?
Turn on your optical camouflage and follow me!
Roger!
What's with that answer?
Batou, how is it there?
I've arrived at the back of the mansion,
and it's crawling with bugs.
Major, I've figured it out.
Only one hit man was hired after all.
Alias Fem.
Fem is a battle cyborg who is a member of the
NanHai Mafia and is wanted internationally.
I've confirmed it by tracing
back the back account,
it seems like the people from the Chinese restaurant
were just trying to distract our investigation.
All right, I'll see the rest on the report later.
You fly over here too.
Roger.
*Sigh* Good thing I was already heading there.
Major, North Port Maintenance has
an appointment at Yokose's mansion.
I've rewritten the appointment and the ID,
so you can go through the front entrance.
Roger, you've done well.
Stay there and watch over the mansion's systems.
Whoa... what bad taste.
Maybe I should take one home.
That was close.
Here I go again.
That one?
Bankers...
Bad timing.
Tachikoma, check that van.
May I have your name please?
Major!
He seems to be dead already.
We're a step behind.
If you don't have an appointment,
will you leave please?
I'm from North Port Maintenance,
I'm here to do the regular inspections.
Thank you for always taking the trouble.
Are there only dolls without ghosts here?
Batou, I've disabled the security system.
Hurry in and protect Yokose.
Fem has already snuck into the house.
Sorry, I might be late.
Hurry up.
Tachikoma, follow me.
May I ask you who you are?
Ah, I'm Tachikoma.
Here I go again.
They probably can't jump up here,
but to kill them one by one would be...
Only that one is a problem.
I'll try this then.
Suspicious-looking person detected.
What am I doing...?
Tachikoma, what were you looking at?
Major, these androids don't have
barriers protecting their brains.
Now, the hit man is...
You haven't forgotten your role
as my clothes, have you?
I didn't mean to forget...
Yokose-sama is sleeping now.
Please wait until he's awake.
I won't wake him up.
What are you doing?
Boy, I finally understand dog's feelings.
Listen guys,
SIT!
Good, okay.
Let's hurry.
What was that?
You're surrounded by the gold you exploited
from the poor, you must be satisfied.
Yokose Kanemoto...
Die by the gold you love so much!
Hold it right there, Fem.
Police.
You'd better surrender.
Shit...
You should've shot Yokose first, shouldn't you?
You're late.
What have you been up to?
You were slacking off.
A few things happened.
But wow, this is great.
This is quite the eye candy.
More like poison for the eyes.
What kind of nerves do you have to not
have been woken up by all this fuss?
He has been dead for at
least three or four months.
Here's some information.
It seems that he programmed
what it should do if he died.
His money-making program has been working...
so nobody could tell that he was dead?
Seems like it, yeah. Now what about this?
It'd be bad if we didn't contact
his lawyers and family, right?
To tell them, 'Your boss is dead.'
I'm afraid he doesn't have any family.
If I remember right,
he said something like that in an interview.
That reminds me, you're familiar with Yokose.
Can you take care of the rest?
Yeah.
Eh?
If there aren't any heirs,
the government will take that bullion.
It's quite unreasonable isn't it?
Isn't it unreasonable to
accumulate so much for oneself?
What are you holding?
You can't possibly take it with you.
Wait.
It's a toll to cross the river Styx.
This money-making program
uses a huge amount of money.
It will be difficult to file a
detailed report until we have the AI.
Do it as soon as possible.
Say, how's the Major?
She's talking with Ishikawa about our bad AI.
Huh?
You have a point there, but can't you input
data like discipline or an admonition?
I know...
but the Tachikomas can't even
comprehend the concept of work.
I'm home.
Ah, welcome back.
Look, look...
I made 100,000 yen on Meditech's stock today.
Did you really buy that?
I'd completely forgotten about that...
Of course!
Financial management is an
important skill for housewives.
Dinner is ready.
Serrano Genomics
- Purchase
- Cancel
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up